[pleasant music playing]
[traffic bustling sounds]
Are you done?
How do I look?
Like a proper, traditional
daughter of the house.
Traditional what?
A traditional woman.
[pleasant music continues]
Are you nervous?
Are you?
Well, it's been almost 3 years.
I wonder how they will receive us.
Trust me. All their anger will
disappear the moment they see you.
I'm sure they will fall
in love with you too.
They have no choice.
I'll keep trying till they do.
Just wait and watch.
I got a whole plan laid out.
Well, don't get your hopes up.
Oh, they're already up.
I want everyone to like me.
Oh...
Is that so?
[sighs]
Actually, I'm scared they
might say something to you.
I mean, you did snatch me
away from my family, after all.
Not my words.
It's what my family would say.
Swarna...
You know I was kidding, right?
Come on.
Grandpa, my husband is a good doctor.
Feel free to get checked.
It's free of cost.
Doctor, my leg hurts all the time.
Please take a look at this.
[overlapping voices]
Everyone will get their turn.
Okay, okay. Calm down.
[laughs]
Stop the bus!
-Veerendar Raju!
-Long Live!
Get down, everyone. The bus
won't go beyond this point.
-Veerendar Raju!
-Long Live!
[traffic bustling sounds]
Sit here.
Swarna, I'll go find something to eat.
Hey, get me a cup of tea.
Block the other side too.
I'm sure you worked very
hard to gather all these people,
and move these stones here.
Of course! We had to wake up at 4 AM.
Please don't mind me asking.
Will his soul rest in peace if
you shut everything down?
What's the logic here?
Not just the roads. Schools,
shops, everything is shut down.
It's a way of paying
respect to his soul.
Respect or peace for his soul?
They are two different things.
Check the other side, guys.
His soul will rest in
peace if we respect him.
[smirks]
Take a tea break, guys.
But until yesterday, people
were using the roads as usual.
All the shops were operating.
Does that mean they were
disrespecting him then?
When he was with us, we were
respecting him directly in person.
Now that he's gone, what's
wrong in showing it like this?
Where did you get these flags?
Rangaiah's tailoring shop.
Oh! So you opened the shops
even after he passed away.
Just for half an hour.
And then we shut it again.
What about the tea and coffee?
Savithramma's
tea shop. So what?
What are you implying?
Half an hour for the flags
and 15 minutes for the tea.
Another 30 minutes for the garlands.
Looks like you've disrespected
him more than any of us.
Are you saying we
disrespected our leader?
Hold on a minute!
What did you just say?
We're disrespecting our leader?
Where are you from, again?
[overlapping clamor]
Swarna, what's going on?
Calm down, guys. Let's talk.
Please calm down.
Stop pushing me!
[hand swishing]
Suri!
Did he just fall in?
Is he alive?
My husband is a good doctor.
[playful music playing]
[traffic bustling sounds]
[bus comes to a halt]
My brother said he'd pick us up.
It's okay. The bus was late, right?
Taxi, taxi!
Taxi!
Swarna, let's go.
[eerie music playing]
Let me get that.
Brother, how are you?
Hey, take this inside.
Sister-in-law, how are you?
Let me take these.
Here you go.
I waited at the bus stop for so long.
But then I had to rush back here.
Our bus was interrupted
by a group of protestors.
Umm... Geetha has been asking for you.
And for sister-in-law, of course.
Please come.
-Listen, I need to tell you something.
-What is it?
Dad doesn't know you're coming.
Are you serious? You said you told him.
I didn't say that.
I said I was going to tell him.
Why didn't you tell him then?
I'll find the right time and tell him.
You come inside. Sister-in-law, let's go.
Swarna...
Priest, the auspicious
time will pass. Let's go.
Sure, sir.
[priest chanting]
I'll read out the wedding invitation now.
Wishing the couple a
blessed and harmonious life,
On the first day of
the bright fortnight...
Mom, look! Big brother's here!
of the month of Jyeshta, in the
lunar year named Krodhanama,
this auspicious time has
been set for the wedding of...
Ramaiah Raju’s second
daughter Venkata Geetha with...
and Uppalapati Madhava
Raju's only son Prakash...
in holy matrimony, with
the blessings of Almighty.
Sir, please exchange
the ceremonial offerings.
[priest continues chanting]
Hello, sister-in-law.
[smiles]
[suspenseful music playing]
Now watch your dad go off at him!
Who called him?
Actually...
I did. I was going to tell you...
You thought I wouldn't be able
to say anything once he's here.
He left this family for that woman.
How could he even show up now?
But our sister deserves to have
her elder brother at her wedding.
-I'll see you.
-Yeah.
Let's go.
We're at a wedding
where we aren't welcome.
They refuse to even talk to me.
It's okay.
Nobody greeted me either.
Anyway, the function is over.
Let's go.
Brother, hello!
Where do you think you're going?
You didn't wish me well or shake
my hand. What is this behavior?
All the best!
The guy looks really good.
I know, right.
Alright then. We'll leave.
Hello, sir! Won't you
stay for the wedding?
I can't manage everything alone.
You have to stay.
You know how dad can be.
Please stay.
Sister-in-law, please.
Let's stay, Ani.
Oh! You call him Ani.
We came all the way.
We might as well stay.
They seem like such good people.
Mom...
Are you taking out your resentment
toward your father on us?
Won't you stay back
for your mother’s sake?
Just wait and see.
We'll become their
favorites within a week.
[sifting rice]
[waving hand fan]
Don't be so sure.
The enquiry commission is yet to begin.
What are you?
What?
I'm Swarna.
That's what you
wanted to know, right?
She's asking about your caste.
Oh, sorry.
Unfortunately, my parents passed away...
before I could know my caste.
I'd have definitely asked
them if they lived a little longer.
That's sad. What about
properties, assets, gold, etc?
Unfortunately, I missed out on that too.
-Did you go to college?
-I did BA Economics.
What's that all about?
Well, Economics is...
It's nothing, grandma.
Few degrees are purely
decorative, and this is one of them.
Let me answer.
Economics is...
Which side are you from anyway?
Side.
It's not caste. So...
She means to ask where you're from.
Your slang is a bit eccentric.
So she wants to know your native place.
We stayed in Tirupati for
a while, and then Nellore.
They're adjacent regions.
What about coo...coo...coo...
Let me say it.
She's asking if you can cook.
[chuckles awkwardly]
When do you wake up in the morning?
Can you make Methi Muttton Masala?
What was your percentage in BA?
Can you do Surya Namaskars?
What about tamarind chicken?
Can you sew?
Can you make rangolis?
Do you have any siblings?
They grilled me like I'm some criminal.
I wonder where he found her.
What's wrong with my accent?
I speak just like you, right?
What was up with that accent?
Oh, god! Was it Tamil or Telugu?
How did you put up with them, Ani?
How is he putting up with her?
Do you think she will mingle with us?
Tamarind Chicken.
Methi Mutton Masala.
Just wait. I will hit them so hard!
With love, Ani.
-All hail...
-Mr. Ramaiah Raju!
[bustling slogans]
-Namaste, sir.
-Namaste.
Please come.
How did the engagement go?
We heard your elder son
and daughter-in-law are here.
Did you send the candidate
list to the party's Head Office?
-We wanted to check with you first.
-Get on it right away.
-Namaste, sir.
-Namaste.
[unsettling music playing]
Please be seated.
Greetings to the candidates
and members of our party.
Namaste, sir.
There have been discussions
with the High Command...
about who should get
the party ticket next.
Only a candidate with
a good public image,
-Hail!
-Madhusudhan Rao.
someone experienced,
-Hail!
-Madhusudhan Rao.
someone deserving,
-Hail!
-Madhusudhan Rao.
someone away from
scams and criminal cases,
-Hail!
-Madhusudhan Rao!
Stop it!
and someone who is
honest, will get the ticket.
Our CM is visiting on the 10th...
to inaugurate the government hospital.
He would be meeting me
and confirming the candidate.
[fax machine buzzing]
How did the paper travel so
far and come out from this?
The CM is visiting next week.
Here are the security details
from the Commissioner's office.
-Note everything down.
-Okay, sir.
If you find anyone suspicious
in the town, bring them in.
Okay, sir.
-Give me the fax manual.
-Here you go, sir.
[overlapping clamor]
[knife whooshing]
Were you a cook before, Karuna?
No.
I simply love chopping stuff.
Where's the appeal in that?
What are your plans
once you get out, Karuna?
When I was a kid, I went
to Paderu this one time.
There, I saw a country
hen at a butcher shop.
It was a well-fed hen,
living happily with its family.
I gave it to this one family I met.
They snapped its neck
right in front of me...
and made chicken curry for me.
Each mouthful was so heavenly that...
it felt like I was consuming
every happy moment...
that the hen has had.
Let's say I get out of here.
I will go hunting for one such hen...
and devour it.
Karuna...
-Sir.
-You have a visitor. Follow me.
Bro, over here.
-I saw Jhansi, bro.
-Be loud, man!
I saw Jhansi!
[alarming music playing]
I think it was her.
Where did you see her?
Near Pamara Junction,
on the Ballavaram Bus.
I'm not sure if it was her.
I thought I would tell you anyway.
How long have you been under me?
A few years now, bro.
Have you learned nothing at all?
What's the most important
thing to me? Huh?
Jhansi, bro.
When you see someone who might be her,
don't you think you should've
followed her and confirmed...
instead of running to
me with your suspicions?
Go back there and confirm if it's her.
Okay, bro.
[heavy breathing]
[prayer bell clinking]
[door creaks]
[grandma praying]
[playful music playing]
Kamakshi, make the elder
daughter-in-law light the lamp.
Apply vermillion.
Here.
Not to me. To the tulasi plant.
Go around it.
This is fun.
Clockwise.
[pleasant music playing]
Go again.
One last time.
Come, light the lamp.
The lamp is down there.
Over there.
What!
Oh, lord!
Now...
Take this.
Light it up.
-Show it to the tulsi plant. Not me.
-I know, I know.
Over there.
What's going on?
Can you sing a prayer?
Can you?
Go ahead then.
Repeat after me, okay?
[singing prayer]
[chanting a prayer]
How did the engagement go?
We definitely missed you.
-How's your dad doing now?
-He's much better.
God bless you!
You also do it.
It's alright.
It's okay.
Stand back.
Fold your hands.
This is Anasuya.
Our younger son's wife.
She's our darling.
That's Anirudh's wife Swarna.
Oh.
Namaste.
I wanted Anirudh to marry
a cultured girl like you.
Guess I'm not that lucky.
Watch and learn what an ideal
daughter-in-law should be like.
I heard you put vermillion
on mom instead of the tulsi.
It has become a hot topic.
Arghhh, stop it!
They were breathing down my neck.
I broke under pressure
and got confused.
What are you even saying?
Stop blaming them
and check yourself first.
I bet they sulk only in front of me.
You should've seen them with Anasuya.
They were smiling with
their teeth wide open.
I just stood there like a loser.
Why did you leave me alone at home?
You should've woken me up.
This is all because of you.
Otherwise, I would've
gotten dressed up too.
Anasuya would look pale in comparison.
There you go! Why do you
compare yourself to her?
She's the only one in this
house who caters to the needs...
of every family member.
Please don't compete with her.
Let's just get out of
here with pass marks.
If there's a 'Perfect
Daughter-in-Law' award, it goes to her.
[music playing on gramophone]
Ganga gave 3 liters of milk today,
Ah, I missed it! You should've called me.
Ganga wouldn't let you touch her.
She's comfortable only with me.
It's okay. You aren't from
here. You wouldn’t know.
Father-in-law...
Your coffee.
"Pearl-like turmeric
lends a glow to her face"
"The vermilion she wears blesses her days"
"Pearl-like turmeric
lends a glow to her face"
Sister-in-law, what have
you done to those flowers?
[laughs]
It's okay, sister.
You aren't from here.
Let me do it.
Dhanush, stop! Just one bite, come on!
Open your mouth.
"The vermilion she wears blesses her days"
Father-in-law, have this rasam instead.
[smirks]
What's wrong?
We have piping hot rasam
straight from the stove.
You aren't from here.
You wouldn’t know.
[oil sizzling]
We had 20 cooks.
There you are! Want this?
-Tasty, isn't it?
-Yeah.
Your aunt Anasuya made
them. They're delicious!
"A woman's true beauty dwells
in the hands that tend her home"
Go on, press her feet!
Her gold necklace is definitely yours now.
That gold necklace is mine
even if I don't press her feet.
Please total it, ma'am.
-Here you go.
-Can I do it?
I studied BA Economics. I can do it.
Alright, here you go.
"Where does lasting prosperity reside?"
"In a house that welcomes
dawn with rangoli"
Swarna, take these inside and...
Oh, you aren't familiar.
Anasuya, please take these inside.
"The vermilion she wears blesses her days"
"Flowers bloom and fruits ripen in
a home touched by love and grace"
Get me one more dosa, dear.
"Pearl-like turmeric
lends a glow to her face"
[chair creaks]
Dad...
-Which way is the post office?
-That way.
[hen cackling]
[telephone ringing]
(Kid) Yay! It's a new TV.
[telephone continues ringing]
Hello? Hello?
What's that noise?
I won 'The Ideal Woman' game show.
They gave me an OnidaTV.
It's getting fixed.
You're happy, right?
That's all I want.
Is everything alright over there?
Not the slightest.
Nobody here likes me.
Relax. They will warm up to you.
There's no time. It has to be quick.
Why don't you come here?
Why? What will I do there?
There's a lady here called Anasuya,
who'd steal that award from you.
I want to be better than her.
If you can help me with
cooking, I'll impress them.
Are you serious?
'The Ideal Woman' should
take care of her best friend too,
not just the husband.
My husband can't survive without my food.
Please try to understand.
Also, I have guests
over to watch the new TV.
Alright. You enjoy cooking
and watching your new TV.
I can't believe you've
forgotten everything.
I thought I would also find a nice family.
I guess I'm not destined for happiness.
Everyone can't have
a happy family like you.
Remember everything that I
did for you when we were kids?
I bought ribbons and
talcum powder for you...
with my savings at the orphanage.
You looked so cute in those
that a couple adopted you...
instead of me.
Why are you digging the past now?
It's just my fate.
I wish I had a friend like myself.
You're being more dramatic...
than Sridevi and Jayaprada.
There's a bigger drama going on here.
I'm literally begging you, can't you see?
Have I ever asked you for anything?
Yes! You're always asking me something.
I meant recently.
Yeah, you did actually.
What about this month?
Just tell me if you're coming or not.
Alright. I'll be there.
Do I have a choice?
Okay.
[Husband] Hey, I'm waiting here.
Coming, dear.
[horn blaring]
[thud]
[bus comes to a halt]
[suspenseful music playing]
Can you make tamarind
chicken and methi mutton masala?
I just arrived. Let me breathe.
I'll freshen up and then get to work.
We don't have the time.
The wedding is soon.
My father-in-law hasn't spoken to Ani yet.
Ani isn't saying it but he's really sad.
I don't have a single talent
that would impress them.
Anasuya is sweeping them away.
Can you make tamarind chicken or not?
It's not really tamarind
chicken but, let me handle it.
But first, let's go home.
-I can't take you home yet.
-Then?
[suspenseful music playing]
The inside is much better.
The room is open, ma'am.
Come.
Are you seriously making me stay here?
It looks nice, see?
I hope you're kidding
because, it's disastrous!
Be optimistic.
It's not working.
Now that you're here,
I know you'll fix everything.
Of course. It's not like I have a choice.
I'll keep you here and run the house.
Keep me here? Sounds suggestive.
I keep you here and run the house there.
The word 'keep' is the problem here.
I'll take your help and run the house.
Anasuya will be perplexed.
Perplexed?
Get ready in 5 minutes.
It's war-time.
Let's come on!
[sighs]
Our village finally has a
wedding venue, all thanks to you.
Your elder son is also in town.
Why don't we have your
daughter's wedding here?
Sure, why not?
Mr. Ramaiah Raju, I heard that you
gave Kesavaiah the contesting ticket.
It's not my individual decision.
Don't say it's the
party leaders' decision.
Why is it that your leaders
always seem to forget me?
You need me for party
funds, for the votes.
But I'm not good enough to contest.
Aren't you supposed to check
his caliber before selecting him?
You should take this
up at the party office.
It's not one's caliber.
It is one's honesty
that gets him the ticket.
Honesty?
We know you're a nice man.
But your niceness only
works on the campaign posters.
People like me to have
to all the dirty work...
for you to get on stage
and woo the public.
It is my money that's
fueling your political career.
I simply came to tell you
to rethink your decision.
Threatening is not my style, sir.
I'm upfront about things.
Good for you.
My father doesn't take
threats seriously anyway.
Considering, he hasn't looted a
single penny in these 30 years.
That's his honesty.
What did you say?
Calm down, people! Step back!
Don't engage with him.
Let's go.
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[door clunks]
Wash the tamarind leaves properly.
Make sure there are no twigs.
Add oil to the pan
and add onions,
cinammon stick, cloves and cardamom.
-How much are these eggplants for?
-2 rupees per kilo, ma'am.
Oh, I almost forgot bengal gram.
That's the main ingredient.
Oh, the one that looks
round and white in color?
Keep these aside. I'll be right back.
I thought you'd have the basic knowledge.
Do I have to explain every ingredient now?
I'll manage using cheat
sheets, like we did during exams.
Otherwise, there's a big
tree by the kitchen window.
You could hide behind
it and tell me what to do.
We'll manage, don't worry.
Be practical.
You seriously think you can do this?
I'll take these.
Why do you want to cook
so desperately anyway?
Give me two of these.
He waited eagerly for 2 years
for his family to accept him.
He left everyone behind for me.
Now, shouldn't I help
him win his family back?
You know he's never asked me for anything.
[eerie music playing]
We need to go.
Come, let's go!
Where? What's wrong?
Wow, the cucumbers are so glossy!
Tomatoes look nice.
How much are these for?
1 rupee per kilo, ma'am.
Come!
Where are you dragging me?
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh, you wanted fish?
That guy in checks has been following us.
Who?
That guy.
Yeah, right. As if you're James Bond.
Someone's watching too many movies.
Let me prove it.
Hold on. Let me get the fish.
I can't teach you how to cook.
Let me go back home.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
He is following us.
Don't look!
Shit! He's really following us.
What do we do now?
I'm scared.
I have only 10 rupees.
He might leave if we say we have no money.
He looks like a thief.
No, don't do it!
Oye!
Why are you following us?
I'm not following you.
But you seem oddly familiar.
What's your name?
It's none of your business.
I've definitely seen you somewhere.
You lived in the forests
before, didn't you?
Do you know who I am?
Do you really know who I am?
Jhansi?
Get lost right now!
If I ever see you again,
I'll blow your brains out!
[upbeat music playing]
Hey! Did you just threaten him?
Be it a hero or a housewife,
when the dialogue lands right,
anyone has to get scared.
Let's go.
You're really unpredictable sometimes.
[crickets chirping]
[telephone ringing]
Sister...
Swarna, is everything okay?
Is he still in jail?
He's been charged for multiple assaults.
He won't come out anytime soon.
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
Swarna, be honest.
I was just getting an update. That's all.
Swarna, listen to me.
[upbeat music playing]
I came to get water.
There's a water pot in your room.
It's empty.
I only filled it last night.
Due to the extreme heat here,
I drank it all.
I'm not from here, remember?
[upbeat music continues]
Something feels off with Swarna.
You're skeptical about
everyone but yourself.
Now go to bed.
[temple bell rings]
Why is the sky draped in blue?
Because red would’ve ruined its beauty.
If you deny I am a poet,
I’ll answer with a blade.
Deny me as a writer,
and I’ll answer with stones.
Who's this poet, girl?
Vagdevi?
[smirks]
Stupid stuff!
Geetha, where's Ani?
Where is he?
He went to the medical
camp early morning.
He even skipped breakfast.
-Here you go, doctor.
-The fee is only one rupee, grandpa.
Don't forget to take these medicines.
Ani...
Did you forget me and breakfast for this?
Are there no other
doctors in this village?
Well, there are no specialists.
So I try to do whatever I
can every time I'm here.
Wow! You're overflowing with kindness.
How can somebody be so nice?
There's got to be a catch, right?
You're the catch.
You're right.
Hi, doctor. How's your father doing?
Yeah, he's fine. I'll be
right there. Please sit.
The whole village
worships your dad, isn't it?
But he doesn't like me.
He hasn't said a word to me till now.
So what? Why don't you go talk to him?
Everything will be sorted
from tomorrow. Trust me.
[birds chirping]
[dramatic music playing]
Savory doughnuts,
sweet pie, tamarind rice,
tamarind chicken, methi
mutton masala, fish curry.
Who made all these, mom?
Why so many dishes?
When did she wake up?
What's happening?
Why did you make so many dishes?
Did you even sleep?
I didn't make these, mother-in-law.
Who did then?
I have no clue.
Sister-in-law!
Was it you?
When did you find the
time to make all this?
I woke up at 3 AM.
I thought I'd make a little
something for the feast today.
My mouth is watering
from just smelling it.
How did you do it? My god!
It's no small feat to
pull off a feast like this.
I know. You must have worked so hard.
Chicken curry, brinjal
curry, ridge gourd chutney.
Let's kill it!
Let's go.
"Pearl-like turmeric
lends a glow to her face"
"The vermilion she wears blesses her days"
"Flowers bloom and fruits ripen in a home
Touched by love and grace"
"Pearl-like turmeric
lends a glow to her face"
"The vermilion she wears blesses her days"
-She gave 4 litres of milk.
-Ganga let you touch her?
You're awesome!
Ganga, how could you!
-Now, would you take a look at that!
-You like it?
-Grandma, come with me!
-Where are you taking me?
Come!
"The sacred tulasi in the
courtyard rewards blessings untold"
How long is it going to take?
Have some patience.
-Do it properly.
-You do it!
Never mind.
Let's start. 1..2..3!
"The gentle cow fills the home
with plenty and well-being"
I can't do this.
No, no. Keep going.
My back is killing me!
"Pearl-like turmeric
lends a glow to her face"
"The vermilion she wears blesses her days"
[whispers] Did you make
gongura prawns well?
I nailed it. Here you go.
Mom, here's dad's BP medicine.
These work better. I switched them up.
Cooking everyday, rangolis and puja...
You're on to something big.
Hell, yeah!
I dare you to figure it out.
[door creaking]
We'll be in trouble if sir finds out.
It's okay. Relax. He's a good guy.
He never makes any demands.
You carry on.
Bro, it's me.
What's the matter?
She's nothing like you described.
She's like any other homemaker.
She seems like her but
not her at the same time.
It's totally confusing, bro!
Give me more details.
Have you ever dealt with someone?
Of course, I do deals all the time.
-Have you taken someone out before?
-Oh, like a date?
Have you killed before?
Oh, you mean 'kill' someone.
You know that builder. Somaraju.
Srinu and I killed him together.
I struck him first though.
Then do one thing.
Go to the market and
ask for a country knife.
Then stab her to death with it.
I'm not sure if it's her.
If you manage to kill
her, then it's not Jhansi.
What if it is Jhansi?
You'll be dead.
Your guy is crazy mad!
Don't mix everything up.
I prayed that I'd visit Venkatapuram
temple if her marriage is fixed.
No one seems to care enough to take me.
Everyone's busy with the wedding chores.
All the men have their respective tasks.
Everyone gets their
works done, except for me.
Hey! I can't watch someone
be sad when I'm in this house.
I know everyone from the
valet to the priest at that temple.
They will give us a VIP experience.
Be ready first thing in the morning.
I'll take you people directly
to the God's chamber.
[birds chirping]
We've reached. Get down.
Get down, mother-in-law.
Careful.
[doors shut]
Swarna, let's go.
See, I made it happen.
Hey, look! That's Buchiraju, isn't it?
-Who's Buchiraju?
-Ramaiah Raju's son-in-law.
How dare they mess with us?
Let's go get him.
Guys, let's go.
[eerie music playing]
[oil sizzling]
Hey!
Didn't you go to the temple?
Your sister-in-law is somehow
cooking everything before I wake up.
So before they return from the temple,
I'm going to cook everything
and impress them.
Wait, don't I get a coffee?
Have it at the station.
[devotional song
playing in the background]
[eerie music continues]
Go ahead and pray, sister-in-law.
[upbeat music playing]
Come, take the harathi (blessings).
-Let's go?
-Yeah. Let's move.
Hurry up! We got to be
home before father-in-law.
-Let's go, let's go.
-Stop rushing us, Buchiraju.
The car is that way.
Bro, two soda.
Here you go.
For them.
[upbeat music intensifies]
[soda cart rattling]
[explosion]
[upbeat music continues]
-They're here to kill us!
-Get in! Hurry up!
There they are! Catch them!
Start the car!
Where's the key?
Get in quickly, guys!
Get in.
I said, get in!
Get in! Let's go!
Guys, stop the car!
[gear shifts]
Where are you going?
[thud]
[gear shifts]
[engine revs]
I told you to go back.
Why did you crash the bike?
Never mind. That was a nice move.
[engine revs]
[bikes revving]
You said you'd take
care of everything.
What do you have to say now?
You were the one who wanted to
visit the temple. Don't blame me now.
-I didn't know you could drive.
-I can wing it.
Wing it?
[yelling]
Son-in-law, why are
these goons chasing us?
We shouldn't have stepped out.
I don't have such violent enemies.
They're catching up!
[bikes revving]
[music intensifies]
[car engine revs]
Keep going.
[thud]
Swarna, careful.
[upbeat music playing]
He pulled out a gun!
He's stuck on the
windshield like a lizard.
[bikes revving]
[screams]
What if we all die here?
There's no female at home to mourn us.
What are you saying?
Anasuya is home only, dear.
Focus there.
Watch out!
Geetha, take the coconut and
wrap a cloth around it tightly.
Alright, alright.
Have you ever catapulted
a stone at a mango tree?
Got it, got it.
They're close. We need to do something.
Hit him! Go for it!
Just do it! You got this!
[grunts]
Watch out!
Just swing it at him! Do it!
[thud]
[screams]
-[Geetha screaming]
-He has a knife!
[knife whooshes]
Careful.
[door clunks]
[screams]
Good-riddance!
What the hell! They're on to us again.
They're overtaking us from that side.
They should forget all about
Swarna once they taste this.
Swarna, they're so close.
[bike revs]
[tires screeching]
[thud]
-They're all down! Thank god!
-No, they're not.
Two guys are charging from the front.
Be ready.
They're close.
Open the door!
[doors clunk]
[thud]
[groans]
The last guy is down too!
You were awesome, sister-in-law!
You drove well.
We almost reached our village.
Should I take the wheel from here?
We're almost home, so...
Buchiraju, you must be
really tired from being so afraid.
One of our girls is about to get married.
You should've checked with me...
before visiting such a far-off temple.
Mom...
Did you come up with this plan?
Grandma told us to ask you first.
But Buchiraju said he's got this.
And that we would be back in no time.
Trust me when I say this.
We wouldn't be alive
if it weren't for her.
Sorry.
See, he didn't say anything
because you're the son-in-law.
If it were someone else,
he'd have lashed out at them.
I know you'd rather take it
upon yourself than see us sad.
Just a minute.
I have a doubt.
Did you think of this beforehand
or come up with it on the spot?
Did I have the luxury
of thinking it through?
I came up with it on the spot.
[telephone clicks]
DSP sir can't do anything.
They aren't even dacoits.
I'm sure Madhusudhan Rao is behind this.
[eerie music playing]
Guess what!
I made your favorite
prawns fry and biryani.
It tastes too good.
That can wait. You know
what happened today?
Swarna drove the car like a pro.
She went vroom vroom.
I made your favorite fish curry, grandma.
We wouldn't have made it without Swarna.
Mother-in-law!
I made your favorite chicken pulao.
I'll taste it in a bit.
-Sravani...
-Mom.
-Call Ani and Swarna to my room.
-Okay, mom.
There's more.
Listen, dear.
I want to pass on the necklace
mother-in-law gave me, to Swarna.
I should've done it when
they first got married.
I guess it's never too late.
He may have married
someone you didn't approve of.
But she's definitely a good person.
Alright.
[cheerful music playing]
When did you learn to drive?
I learned as I kept driving.
I drove as I kept learning.
This is a family heirloom passed
on to the first daughter-in-law.
I know it's long overdue.
Well, it's finally time.
-See how she impressed her.
-Hmm.
Her and everyone else.
Try it on, love.
It will look beautiful on you.
They're all such nice people.
It feels wrong to deceive them.
Oh. So you're going
to tell them the truth?
Or I could fully transform
into the Swarna they think I am.
That way, I wouldn't have to
tell them the truth anymore.
Please teach me all the recipes
you know quickly. Chop, chop!
Chop, chop?
[dramatically] It's many generations
of knowledge and years of practice.
Do you think this is a joke?
Cooking is a form of penance
performed in front of the stove.
Your eyes and hands should
burn, you must shed blood.
Have you ever seen blood at least?
I thought so!
Only then you can make these
traditional recipes you dream of.
Is there so much to it?
Alright. Teach me at least
one recipe in your style.
Not happening. I'll teach
you something in your style.
Thanks.
[crickets chirping]
[door creaks]
I'll learn this recipe as well.
There's still time for that.
Take this inside for now.
[door creaks]
It's the last house over there.
Who is it at this time of the night?
[scooter engine revving]
-Are you scared?
-Shut up!
So many guys to kill one woman?
-Aren't I enough?
-Just shut up!
The job should be done
today no matter what.
Otherwise Karuna will kill us!
Guys, come on!
[eerie music playing]
[metal clunks]
Let's sneak into the house slowly.
It's her, guys. Hide.
Let me ask her once again.
Jhansi!
Why is he cat-calling
her instead of attacking?
Apparently, if he's able
to kill her, she's not Jhansi.
What if it is Jhansi?
Then apparently, he will die.
Guys, stop chatting and get to business.
[eerie music builds up]
Jhansi!
Are you Jhansi or not?
Answer me!
You're back?
Who the hell are you, man?
I'm asking you one last time.
Are you Jhansi or not?
Say yes, and I'll leave.
Otherwise, I'd have to kill you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[thud]
[knife whooshes]
[screams]
[thud]
I think that's Jhansi.
[thud sounds continue]
She's definitely Jhansi.
What are you guys looking at? Come on!
[thud sounds continue]
Who are you guys?
Get the hell out of here!
[groaning]
Shush!
[thud]
[groans]
What are you still
doing here? Get lost!
Hey!
If you ever show me your face again,
I'll kill you!
Take him away!
[groaning continues]
Get out of here!
Bugger off!
[scooter revs]
Damn it!
It's okay. At least she spared our lives.
[grunts]
I'll get my revenge.
Don't be an idiot.
You're hopeless, man.
[door creaks open]
[knife whooshes]
[thud]
[music intensifies]
Swarna!
Gongura mutton...
[body thuds]
Kiranmayi.
Wake up!
[sharp breathing]
Kiranmayi.
It's okay. Nothing happened.
You're fine.
Keep breathing. Keep breathing.
Slowly.
How can I breathe with a
dead body in front of me?
Shhh! Slowly.
Listen to me. Everything
is absolutely fine.
Hey!
Now...
The thief who followed us at the market,
he sneaked into the home.
So what? You'll kill him?
Keep it low.
I didn't kill him.
He caused his own death.
How is it possible that he came
home and caused his own death?
He's been stabbed.
Oh, no! I didn't stab him.
His knife stabbed him only.
How can an inanimate object stab him?
So, he came running.
He sprained his ankle,
fell on the knife and died.
Which exactly means you killed him.
You're not getting it.
Look at me.
I was walking.
He came on to me like this.
And then he slipped
and fell on his own knife.
Will you help me or not?
What help?
Let's go to the police.
No police. No police.
You believed me because I'm your friend.
If they don't believe me,
I'll become a murderer.
The whole family will be humiliated.
Especially with the wedding coming up.
I don't mind helping
with rangolis and cooking.
But a dead body!
I knew it.
My life has been tough since childhood.
Shut up! Just shut up!
Tell me what to do.
[water splatters]
Grab the rope.
Place your finger.
Where?
[eerie music playing]
Hold the feet. That side is lighter.
You can't tell between
types of dal but you know this!
Pick it up.
Slowly, slowly.
[grandma murmuring chants]
Oh, lord! Help us.
Statue.
Let's go. Let's go.
[footsteps thudding]
[heavy breathing]
Don't tell me you're going
to kill grandma as well.
Shut up!
[glass clinks]
Bloody cat! No sense of time!
[door creaks]
Kiranmayi, we'll go that way.
I can't do it.
-Just 5 more steps.
-No way!
It's easily 500 steps.
Kiranmayi, let's come on!
Let's come on!
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
I'm done!
You go ahead.
Never mind. You can't lift it alone.
Close the door.
-Push the car.
-Huh?
The engine sound will wake
people up. Now push it!
[car engine revs]
[tires screeching ]
[door clunks]
[thud]
[water splatters]
[sighs]
[car engine revs]
[melancholic music playing]
What happened here?
I used to make so many desserts with this.
Do you think it shrunk because of heat?
No. It looks more like...
someone's head has been...
[thud]
whacked with it.
I mean, for it to bend like this,
someone like me must have hit it hard.
Who else could it be?
-Where did you find this?
-On the front porch.
How did it end up there?
Yeah, I wonder.
I must be so dumb if it took
me this long to figure it out.
My mind was so foggy after
what happened yesterday.
But I'm ready for it now.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to drag you into this.
Where do I begin?
Life was good when we lived
together at the orphanage.
We were inseparable.
Do you remember the hostel warden?
That monster?
I was happy that you
found a nice family...
and got out of that misery.
But once you left,
I became his target.
I couldn't stay there
anymore and so, I ran away.
I didn't know where to go.
But I had to get out of there.
Maybe this journey was
meant to strengthen me.
I sought shelter at various places.
I did every job I could find.
No one showed me any kindness.
I pursued distant education while
I was working at this one place.
But there was this
scoundrel over there as well.
Swarna...
He would try really hard to exploit me.
I would be shivering with fear all night.
But then...
there's only so many times
or places I can run away to.
One night, a bunch of people showed up.
You guys go carefully.
We'll be here for 4 days.
They were hiding from the police.
They stayed for a couple of days.
I couldn't tell if they were
good people or bad people.
They were fearless, for sure.
That was the first time...
I saw how fearless people looked.
I thought I was getting a read on them.
Little did I know that one of them
was watching me very closely.
Remember. We're doing it
for those who face injustice.
You can achieve your
goal only if you let go of fear.
It felt like he was
directly talking to me.
I decided to overcome
my fear and fight back.
[intense music sets in]
[door creaks]
Oh!
You left the door open for me.
You finally got my hints?
[gasps]
No, don't!
[knife whooshes]
[screams]
[groans]
[shrill cry]
If 5 people mourn his death,
there are 30 who celebrate it.
Remember this math, always.
If the math makes sense to you,
forget about grief, and whether
it's something wrong to do.
Will you join us?
I spent my whole life being
aimless and directionless.
When they asked me to join them,
I didn't think if it was right or wrong.
I left with them.
My life had completely changed.
Including my name.
Jhansi.
That's your name from today.
[bikes revving]
It doesn't matter if our
target is rich or powerful.
If he has wronged, I
will make him pay for it.
They're from the neighboring village.
Jhansi...
[intense music playing]
When you spend all
your life feeling unloved,
you settle for bare
minimum and call it love.
You're really special, Jhansi.
I'm glad I found you.
I'll train you like a warrior.
[gun clicks]
[music intensifies]
[gun shot fired]
[thud]
[revolver clicks]
[exploding]
It didn't occur to me back then...
that he's a wolf hiding behind
the mask of a good man.
He hand picked me with the intention of...
moulding me as per his agenda.
We all came together for
the common good, until...
Karuna, who are they?
You sold your soul, Karuna.
But he used us for his selfish purposes.
One day, while the
police were chasing us...
You're safe only as long as you obey him.
Once you go against him,
he will get his revenge
when the time is right.
Jhansi, run!
[gun shots firing]
[grunts]
Leave him! Run, run!
Karuna, please help!
Karuna!
Karuna, please!
[gun shots continue firing]
Shiva wasn't spared either,
even though he was like a brother to him.
He's dead because of you.
He came back because he fancied you,
and got himself killed.
He blamed me for his mistake.
I didn't get his intentions back then.
[crying]
I was shattered that Shiva
was dead because of me.
Fear slowly started creeping back in.
I brought your favorite
idli karam podi. Have it.
Whatever I say is for your own good.
You'll see it someday.
Men like him suppress you
and turn you into puppets,
while pretending to be
innocent, loving men.
But the truth is,
he's been looking for someone like me.
Someone who has lost everything in life.
I decided that night...
to break free from there.
But he sensed it somehow,
and kept watching me closely.
He built these walls around me...
and controlled my movements 24X7.
I couldn't do anything
but watch his atrocities.
[gun shots fired]
I was slowly dying inside.
That's when I decided
to get him arrested...
even if it meant losing my life.
[intense music playing]
He thought he saved
all of us from the police.
The fact that I trusted...
such a monster blindly...
makes me so angry...
and disgusted by myself.
He committed so many
atrocities right in front of my eyes.
I just stood there, watching.
Was it out of fear?
Or something else?
I just know that...
I felt hopeless.
It took me a lot of time
to recover from that.
I can neither forget...
nor forgive myself.
So I thought it was best to
erase those memories from my life.
I never told anyone about these things.
Not you.
Not Ani.
The fact that you survived all this...
and restarted your life is unbelievable!
I wouldn't have been able to do it.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you, Swarna.
Now some guy is stalking
me and trying to attack me.
I have a feeling Karuna is behind this.
Brother...
Venkanna is dead.
I guess I finally found Jhansi.
[intense music builds up]
If he gets to know where I am,
he'll go to any lengths to come find me.
[steam hissing]
[knife whooshes]
Oh, lord! Someone stabbed Srinu!
He's bleeding heavily. Guys, help!
[intense music continues]
[gas hissing]
[metal clanks]
[matchstick strikes]
[explosion]
Who is this?
-She's my childhood friend.
-Friend?
Did you come with all your stuff?
My husband and I got into a huge fight.
He yelled, I yelled back.
He yelled loudly,
I yelled back a little less loudly.
He was coming towards
me with his hand raised.
I panicked and hit him
before he could hit me.
I realized later that he
wasn't coming to hit me.
He was just trying to
turn on the fan switch.
I left the house because I
was worried that he would.
It's alright.
If he ever decides
to hit you in the future,
he will think twice.
So, what did you and
your husband fight about?
Hey, don't get personal.
You can stay here as long as you'd like.
Feel at home.
You're Swarna's friend,
and that makes you family.
Take her inside, Swarna.
So, this is your cooking
and rangoli set-up.
Don't say set-up. It sounds wrong.
You two are unbelievable!
Sister-in-law, I figured a
secret about your cooking.
You taught her how to cook, didn't you?
You taught me to cook, huh?
You can't resist cooking, can you?
You have to show off your talent.
If you can't resist,
just add salt in the end.
But don't get excited and cook like me.
Cook like you? Are you serious?
Hey! Your friend's
fish curry is delicious!
-I only taught her.
-Really?
Okay. Let me see what else she made.
"Our little girl with the
twin braids is a bride now"
"Yet you're still the same as ever"
"Everyone knows that
stubborn streak of yours"
"You still charge through
life without a care"
"We've been hearing
the whispers everywhere"
"Tell us, how did you manage
to get the man you wanted?"
"How long are you going to
sit there all shy and quiet?"
"Come on, sweetheart"
"Why wait? Let's show them who we are"
"Walking in like queens"
"Bride, what's the rush?"
"The best part is yet to come"
"Attagirl! We're not holding back"
"A girl should have a little spirit"
"Attagirl! Let the smiles spill over"
"This is our celebration
Who's going to stop us?"
"Have the time of your life"
"Let's see what marriage does to you"
"Though I doubt it'll tame your mischief"
"Don't worry, I'll transform
my mother-in-law"
"Into an older version of me"
"Alright girls, enough of the commotion"
"The auspicious time is slipping away"
"That's enough of your playful antics"
"These tricks won't fly
at your in-laws' house"
"Oh, come on! I'm still
the Queen of my house!"
"Attagirl! We're not holding back"
"A girl should have a little spirit"
"Attagirl! Let the smiles spill over"
"This is our celebration
Who's going to stop us?"
"Have the time of your life"
"In this garden of happiness,
as I come into bloom"
"Is my past going to
float around off shore?"
"Oh, come on! You're still
the Queen of our house!"
"Attagirl! We're not holding back"
"A girl should have a little spirit"
"Attagirl! Let the smiles spill over"
"This is our celebration
Who's going to stop us?"
"Have the time of your life"
[PA over loudspeaker] Don't you
see my blood burning with rebellion?
Don't you hear the roaring of my heart?
Don't you see the embers
of revolution flare up?
Don't you hear my voice
cutting through the air?
What are you still waiting for?
Why are you holding back?
Pierce those cloaks of darkness
Step forward with ferocity
Break your shackles of submission
Clench your fist and march ahead
Come, crush the oppressor’s might
Don't you see my blood
burning with rebellion?
Don't you hear the roaring of my heart?
Don't you see the embers
of revolution flare up?
Don't you hear my voice
cutting through the air?
What are you still waiting for?
Why are you holding back?
Pierce those cloaks of darkness
Step forward with ferocity
Break your shackles of submission
Clench your fist and march ahead
Come, crush the oppressor’s might
Don't you see my blood
burning with rebellion?
Don't you hear the roaring of my heart?
[thud]
[thud sounds continue]
Did Karuna send you?
Yes.
I would've showed up if he called.
Where is he now?
At the river bank.
[gun clanks]
[eerie music playing]
Out!
I told you she'd hear my
voice and come running.
[eagle shrieking]
You look ravishing!
You haven't changed a bit.
I have trained you well.
Come close.
Come.
It's been so many years, Jhansi.
[sighs]
I don't go by that name anymore.
Everyone here calls me Swarna.
Who do you mean by everyone?
-My family.
-Family?
Who all are there?
I got married, Karuna.
Holy crap!
You got married?
The one thing I was dreading
to hear, and here goes.
[shrieking in frustration]
Are you really married?
Really?
I gave you this life.
I taught you everything you know.
I made sure the cops didn't get to you.
But someone tipped them about me.
You were on my mind all day...
even when I was in jail.
I wanted to marry you once I got out.
I never confessed my
love but, you knew, right?
I thought you'd take one look
at me and come running.
But now...
I don't know why you're here, Karuna.
Do I have to spell it out for you?
Karuna, listen.
It's thanks to you...
that I could turn over a new leaf.
Let things...
stay as they are.
New life, huh?
You're right.
I'm sure you told your
family about your old life.
You did, right?
Oh, you didn't?
You must have told your husband at least.
Jhansi, are you serious?
Not even your husband knows?
You poor thing.
Don't panic.
I won't tell him.
Karuna...
Leave me alone.
I have a family now.
Why are you begging me so desperately?
I can't see you like this.
Karuna... Karuna, please.
Leave me alone.
Alright, stop begging.
I can't see you like this. I will leave.
You be happy.
Go.
Can I trust you?
-You will leave, right?
-I promise.
Satisfied?
[eerie music sets in]
God forbid something
happens to your family...
I pray that it doesn't.
But God forbid!
Who's going to save them?
Swarna or Jhansi?
Go, go.
Your family must be looking for you.
[intense music playing]
When are we going back home?
We decided to stay
till the wedding, right?
Of course.
The wedding.
What's wrong, Swarna?
Why do you look so worried?
Did someone say something?
We'll talk about it later.
You don't have to hesitate with me.
Tell me what's bothering you.
There's a lot to tell you, Ani.
Yes, I came here to tell you.
But now's not the time.
I'll wait until after the wedding.
I'll tell you everything.
Alright.
[crickets chirping]
Family!
What the hell does that mean?
Aren't I her family?
Then why did you send
her away with good wishes?
I know.
I know I spoke like an idiot.
But I'm not.
Why would I let her go?
She is mine.
Mine!
Let me have a little fun with her.
Who is her husband, what does he do,
who all are in the family, and
what are their weaknesses.
Get me all the information
before I get sober.
[on tape recorder] Don't you see
my blood burning with rebellion?
Don't you hear the roaring of my heart?
This is the song that I heard, sir.
[button clicks]
8 years ago, when I was
posted in Ananthapur,
they played the same song
all over the village back then.
Within the next few days,
the local MLA was shot dead.
Probably, they're using
this song as a warning.
[alarming music playing]
Who are they warning now, sir?
The CM meeting is in 2 days.
Call the Commissioner's Office
and get all the gang details.
Yes, sir.
CM has approved your nomination.
He is going to be present
for the campaigning.
I think it's advisable to give
the party ticket to someone else.
Even my health isn't
keeping up these days.
So, what are you proposing we do now?
There are far more experienced
candidates in the party.
You mean Madhusudhan Rao?
Got it.
You may leave.
Please forgive me.
Looks like Madhusudhan
is back to his old groove.
He's crossing the line
and testing my patience.
Let's show him what we can do.
Pull all the files on the liquor scam.
Let's go.
[bikes rev]
[suspenseful music playing]
How dare he expose my liquor scam files!
Ramaiah Raju ain't a saint, is he?
He's so jealous of my popularity
in public, he resents me.
Who doesn't have a dirty past?
I'm sure he does too.
I'll go digging too.
I will give him a taste of...
Who is he?
Who the hell are you?
Let me speak.
It's a business deal.
People like us have a
history of erasing lives.
And that comes with fear.
When we give some of this fear
back to them, they start fearing us.
-We control them.
-Hey!
What the hell are you talking about?
Ramaiah Raju is going to submit
your files to the CM tomorrow morning.
Liquor scam.
The files only talk about 10 crores.
If they dig deeper, they will
get to the remaining 20 crores.
Further digging, and the murder
you committed for it will also be out.
You guys step outside. Go.
See all those men?
What are you going to
do differently that we can't?
There was an Inspector called
Sridhar Naidu in your constituency.
Remember him?
He suffered sudden death one day.
The Paderu Bridge also
happened to collapse the same day.
It was sensational news back then.
There's a 300 kilometer distance
between the two locations.
But one guy is behind both the incidents.
Having a gang is one thing.
Utilizing them is another.
I'm a free man who is
dead in the police records.
Practically, a ghost.
The only person who
can help you at this time.
Let's say the scam files reach the CM.
What do you want?
[glass clinks]
Can I be of any help?
Umm... These are all scam files, dear.
Hold on.
[papers rustling]
[intense music playing]
CM's meeting will be wrapped by 5 PM.
We will have only 10 minutes of his time.
You forgot this.
Everything will go smoothly.
Let's go.
[car door clunks]
Once this symbol goes up,
everyone in the village knows that...
a person in that house
has a target on their back.
[gun shot fired]
Jhansi, shall we play a game?
Your family is in danger.
Will you reveal your identity now...
or still keep it hidden?
[alarming music playing]
Where's Anirudh?
He went to the hospital.
He asked me to tell you.
What about Sharath?
He went to the police station.
The CM meeting is today, remember?
What happened, love?
-Nothing. Just asking.
-Sister!
You said you'd make
Nellore fish curry for everyone.
I'm kind of busy now.
Let's make it Swarna.
You know we make a good team.
You relax.
You can't make it
better than Swarna.
Sister, you do the cooking.
Okay. I'll buy fish and come.
[vehicle rattling]
I want to watch and learn
how you pick good fish.
Let's go?
Come.
CM is arriving in 30 minutes.
Comb the whole area one more time.
Arrest anyone that you find suspicious.
Where are we going?
You're covering the whole
village like you know the place.
Are you listening?
[eerie music builds up]
Who do you think is the target, Jhansi?
The strongest in the
family should die first.
Your brother-in-law.
Agree?
The fish market is this way.
-Swarna!
-Which way is the police station?
That way.
Stop, stop!
[tires screech]
The strongest guy is of no use to us.
It should be someone whose
death would break your heart.
Your husband.
He should be the one to die.
What's wrong?
We get better fish
near Anirudh's hospital.
Let's go there.
[vehicle engine revving]
No, that's not right.
The Head of the Family should die
first, so that the whole family collapses.
I'll kill him.
Swarna!
What happened?
[suspenseful music playing]
Why are you going towards the rally?
I'm talking to you!
Where did you bring me?
Swarna, will we find fish here?
-Hey!
-Hold on.
[suspenseful music continues]
Hey!
Where are you going? Wait for me.
Are you playing with me?
What's going on? You're
clearly not here for fish.
You can't fool me.
Listen, I have no idea how
to make Nellore fish curry.
In fact, I can't make any kind of curry.
Go do whatever you
want with that information.
Just call for a
rickshaw and go home.
How long, brother?
We've been here for an hour.
Let the CM arrive.
The crowd will go bonkers,
giving us the perfect opportunity
to nab Ramaiah Raju.
[footsteps thud]
-Go back.
-What are you saying?
Have you lost it?
Who are you? Get out!
Let her stay, man. She looks nice.
I won't be quiet if you
mess with my family.
Tell this to Karuna.
Start the bus and go
towards the outskirts.
Who do you think you are?
Get the hell out!
You heard him!
[dramatic music playing]
[thud]
Start the bus!
[gear shifts]
[knife whooshes]
[thud sounds continue]
-Stop the bus!
-Don't stop!
[glass shattering]
[bus comes to a halt]
Keep driving and don't look back.
-All hail...
-Our beloved CM!
[sirens blaring]
[bustling slogans]
Sir, this has the details...
pertaining to Madhusudhan
Rao's liquor scam.
Brother...
I'm sure you told your
family about your old life.
You didn't?
Not even your husband knows?
That's sad!
He knows that you haven't
told your family anything.
He will use that fear against you...
and play games with you.
[gun shot fired]
Your family is in danger.
Will you reveal your identity now...
or still keep it hidden?
[intense music playing]
Are you sad that the plan failed, Karuna?
I didn't get out of jail to
be Madhusudhan's puppet.
Is that how you see me?
Creating a mess in the
bus with all those men!
You call that a plan?
He was stupid to execute it.
But where was your common sense?
We're slowly making Swarna
realize the Jhansi side of her.
That's what I'm here for.
She's just like us.
You boasted about your bus plan.
But it was one big failure.
You just added fuel to fire.
Go on! Enjoy your food!
The CM has the files now.
It's over for me.
The police will be here to arrest me.
You think I'll let this pass?
You think?
If I go to jail, you make
sure to destroy his family.
None of them should be alive.
Kill each one of them.
Take my men if necessary.
How many men do you need?
Answer me, damn it!
Sit down.
Sit down!
We'll do everything you just said.
But I'll decide the time.
She asked me to leave
and boarded some bus.
She's a rare fish. You need
a bigger net to catch it.
I make mind blowing fish curry.
Should I?
[sneaky laugh]
I know why that spatula was bent.
We figured out what
you and Swarna are up to.
What are you staring at?
Speak up!
Swarna didn't do it on purpose.
He only fell on the knife.
Fell on the knife? What are you saying?
Whose knife, and who fell on it?
We saw him outside the
house couple of days back.
But yesterday, he directly
barged into the house.
As if she doesn't have
enough problems already.
Yeah, right. What problems?
Do you know how tough
it is to live in the woods?
What was she doing in the woods?
Forget I said that.
That was the old Swarna.
Old Swarna? As opposed to the new Swarna?
I don't like this, you
holding me hostage here.
I'm leaving!
Stop!
Come back!
Old Swarna.
New Swarna.
[fax machine buzzing]
The bus was right there till then.
It was filled with goons.
I stepped aside to inform
them and the bus was gone.
I think they were planning something big.
But then they left for some reason.
Why did the plan fail?
Who is behind this?
[dramatic music playing]
Swarna?
Swarna, hold up. I forgot
to tell you something.
I didn't do it intentionally.
They forced it out of me.
They took me into the room
and held me hostage. I got scared.
Whom did you tell?
And what did you tell?
It was Anasuya and Buchiraju.
That's the least of my worries.
I'm more worried about what
Karuna is going to do at the moment.
Dhatri, come here.
Now I have to speak to the
one person I didn't want to.
But he's a cop.
I'll only tell him what's important.
I need to talk to you.
What do you have to say?
I got hold of your old police records.
I know everything about you.
I wouldn't be so sure.
[upbeat music playing]
Mr. Raju...
How are you doing?
Namaste.
-Who are you, if I may ask?
-I'm Karuna. Swarna's cousin.
Oh, you came at a good time.
Glad to meet you.
You must have lunch
before you go. I insist.
Didn't you tell them I was coming?
Why didn't I know he was coming, dear?
Kamakshi...
Come here.
This is Swarna's cousin.
That's lovely.
Did you just arrive?
I was in the vicinity.
I thought I'd see Jhan... Swarna and go.
That's sweet of you.
Please have lunch and go.
Swarna, please take care of that.
-Dear, we need you there.
-Let's go.
-Take care of him, Swarna.
-Hope you enjoy the lunch.
What is it?
Do I look nice?
It's our family function, right?
I had to dress up.
[water trickling]
What the hell are you doing, Karuna?
You gave me your word.
Why did you come back?
Come on!
You've been going on and on about family.
I came to see what the hype is about.
Watching all this, I feel
like I want a family too.
Swarna!
Is this your husband?
Swarna, you didn't tell me
your brother was coming.
Cousin.
Where's the lunch being served?
Please follow me.
[eerie music playing]
Look. Who is that?
Swarna's cousin.
We'll know everything if we talk to him.
You also come sit with me.
I saved a chair for you.
It's been a while since we ate together.
Go talk to him.
Let her leave.
Come, come.
[smiles awkwardly] Namaste.
I'm Buchiraju.
She's Anasuya.
Namaste. Here's some brinjal curry.
We heard you're Swarna's close family.
You know her since childhood, right?
What do you want?
Swarna hasn't told us
anything about her childhood.
So, we thought we would ask you.
A lot has happened.
We're all ears!
Things that happened to
her or things that she did?
What do you want to know?
Both sides are terrifying.
Swarna, come here!
[eerie music playing]
Taste the brinjal. It's nice.
What's that? Give me some.
I have a lot of work to do.
The sambar is yummy. Have it.
Alright. Give me some.
Give me two vegetable pieces.
Exactly two?
I'll serve. You go.
There you go.
Is it enough?
[eerie music continues]
Sister-in-law, let's click a picture?
Swarna's cousin, right?
Are you married?
We're ready.
You look lovely.
Let me find a girl for you.
Do you have any preferences?
Let's click against this background.
Swarna.
Someone like Swarna.
Grandma, aunt is looking for you.
Go.
You left me hanging back there.
Finish the story, please?
You said it's terrifying and all.
Sister-in-law, face the camera.
[camera shutter clicks]
[knuckles crack]
Well, don't you think you
should finish the story?
I'll break your bones
if you keep sticking...
your nose into everything.
Understood?
Yes, yes.
Are you feeling sleepy?
Jhansi!
You better leave!
You told a million
lies to enter this family.
Yet, you're threatening me openly.
Very dramatic!
This is why I like you.
I said leave!
Alright, I will.
-I came here to tell you something.
-Don't yell!
Should I tell you here or in private?
What is it?
[thud]
[gasping]
Will you finally drop the act now?
[grunts]
What the hell are you doing, Jhansi?
Serving sambar to everyone.
You think this is what you're meant to do?
[spits]
I revived a dying person
and nurtured her. That's you!
If there's anything special
about you, it's because of me.
Now you'll leave me for family?
What's so great about a family?
Everyone in this world does this.
Love, marriage, baby shower, kids.
Removing their lice,
washing their asses.
You came back to life for this?
Most of us live in a
bubble and die in a bubble.
Quit this cooking nonsense.
Meditate for 5 minutes.
You'll realize what you're doing in life.
Swarna... Swarna...
Your devoted husband
is looking for you. Go.
I was planning to kill your husband,
your in-laws, and everyone else.
But I'm giving you one last chance.
Once you're done here, come back to me.
[creepy laugh]
I came to your house,
had lunch among everyone,
and now I'm talking
to you in your bedroom.
Think about what else I can do.
Go.
Oi!
If you don't come,
I'll come for all their lives.
Pack your bags tonight and come to me.
Swarna...
-Where were you?
-I was right here.
I'll be back.
Ani!
Can you get me a ride to
the bus stop? I'm running late.
[bike revs]
[intense music sets in]
Do you think she will show up, Karuna?
I explained it to her slowly and sweetly,
in a way she would understood.
She will show up.
She has no choice.
[footsteps thudding]
[melancholic music playing]
Take this tablet in the morning.
[dramatic music playing]
Ever since I have been with you,
I have started liking myself.
I was scared that if you
find out about my past,
you wouldn't look at me the same anymore.
Maybe you would've understood.
But I...
I didn't have the courage.
The fact that you didn't
tell me any of this...
hurts me more.
[melancholic music playing]
[bike revs]
Swarna, hold on.
What do we do about Karuna?
Our fight isn't over.
I'm still angry.
But let's deal with him first...
and go back to our argument.
I'll talk to my dad.
He knows some big names.
Or we could talk to the police.
I did already.
I spoke to Sharath.
I need to talk to you.
I know you have no reason to believe me.
But we have a huge danger coming our way.
Only you can help us.
Without any evidence?
There is evidence.
Let's click against this background.
Sir, Sharath here.
He is alive, sir.
I'm sending the evidence right now.
Give this at the DSP's
office. It's urgent.
I wish everything went to plan.
But Karuna is unpredictable.
If something goes wrong,
our family will be targeted.
Ani...
I'll walk away.
That's better.
Why did you fight for my family then?
Your family?
They're my family too.
Exactly!
Then how can you walk away?
You fought alone this whole time.
But now you have me.
We'll handle this together.
[emotional music playing]
[wedding bells ringing]
[suspenseful music sets in]
The job is done.
We're moving him to
the Central Jail tonight.
Yes, sir. We just got the arrest warrant.
[sirens blaring]
Let's put this behind us.
It's over now.
No, Ani.
There's one last thing that I need to do.
[vehicle engine revs]
[eerie music sets in]
[handcuffs clinking]
[gun shots fired]
[vehicle thuds and crashes]
Why did you hide the truth for so long?
To be honest,
I didn't have the courage to do it.
A lie gave me such a
beautiful family that...
I didn't mind hiding the truth.
Why are you coming clean now?
I thought my past was my problem.
But the same past has
come to haunt my family now.
We were happy to
welcome you into the family.
But now you're talking guns and forests.
I don't even know what to make of it.
I've never had anyone
that I could call family.
Nobody taught me anything.
I learned from my personal
mistakes, challenges and betrayals.
I taught myself everything I know.
I'm not defending myself here.
I'm just telling you how things were.
You treated me like your own,
though I was an outsider.
I experienced what it's like to
have a family for this short period.
But it often dawned upon me that...
a dishonest person like me...
isn't deserving of the
'daughter-in-law' title in your family.
I saw a matrimonial ad
looking for a bride once.
She should be beautiful, soft-spoken,
be able to cook, sing and sew, they said.
It was a long list.
A daughter-in-law should have all
these qualities to be the ideal woman.
But I had none of those.
If everyone were the best,
there's no chance a person
like me would find a good home.
But then,
I met Ani.
He let me be my authentic self.
[melancholic music playing]
[crying]
But if you really think about it,
I do have one quality.
Come what may,
I would risk my life to protect my family.
Maybe this isn't an ideal
quality for a daughter-in-law.
Everyone wants to welcome the Goddess
of Prosperity into their home but...
Answer this.
You posed a major threat to this family.
What do you have to say to that?
Even I posed a major threat to
this family due to my political career.
But nobody questioned me then.
Did you forget that she
saved everyone the other day?
We called her family when she saved us.
But when things got risky,
you want to abandon her?
[dramatic music playing]
Not everyone needs to
be a Goddess of Prosperity.
Goddess of Destruction exists too.
[fuse blows]
[gasps]
Hey, get the lantern.
What's going on?
Something is about to go down.
I was really sad listening to all that.
I'm sorry for pestering
with you many questions.
It's okay, Anasuya.
I didn't take any of it to heart.
Umm... listen.
I bothered you a lot about
your recipes, rangolis, and so on.
-Please forgive me.
-Anasuya, listen. We're friends now.
We'll discuss this later, okay?
Please don't mind.
We're friends too.
I'll go talk to her.
[vehicles revving]
They're Madhusudhan Rao's men.
[thud]
[knife whooshes]
[thud sounds continue]
[glass shatters]
[screams]
Get water!
[glass bottles clinking]
Brother, careful!
[fire fizzes out]
Don't be scared.
Do you think they left?
Let's get out of here before it's late.
The trouble has just begun.
[suspenseful music playing]
Guys, go in there and
put on a good show me.
I'll be watching from here.
Listen to me carefully.
Nobody is going to get hurt.
First, we need to close
all the doors and windows.
Yeah, let's do that.
If we do that, we won't be able
to tell where they're entering from.
You're right. Let's keep them all open.
Then they will enter from all sides.
Alright. You tell us what to do.
Go ahead.
They're just trying to scare us.
If we panic,
they'll barge in and attack all of us.
Karuna will play this out like a game.
That's how he operates.
So no matter what, we
need to stick together.
Yeah, but what do we do?
First, we need to close
all the doors and windows.
That's what I said.
Except for this door.
[door creaks open]
We'll hide the elderly and
the children in the corner room.
Hurry up! Get into the bedroom, fast!
Grandma...
Gather all the weapons we have.
What weapons are you talking about?
Knifes, crowbars, pestles, ladles,
Whatever you can find, basically.
Come on, guys! Grab whatever you can.
-Does a sickle work?
-Perfectly.
-What about a ladle?
-Works.
Hurry up!
We'll make chilli bombs.
Wrap chilli powder in small packets.
[knife whooshes]
[gasps]
It's time to go sever their heads!
You all hide safely.
I'll be back with their severed heads.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
Where the hell are you going?
Swarna is alone. I need to go help her.
Oh, no!
[door shuts]
Go, get in.
Get me a cup of tea.
-Don't move, guys.
-I got this. Be careful.
Be safe. Don't leave this room.
Lord, help us!
[door creaks]
Hey, come this way!
[door creaking]
Father-in-law, let them in.
[gun shots fired]
You bunch of idiots!
Why did you enter without a plan?
[fuse crackles]
Attack at once!
[thud]
Dad, come here.
[door clunks]
-Oh, no! What happened?
-Don't worry. He'll be fine.
-What happened to you?
-Dad, sit down.
Fight me if you can!
I'll show you who Buchiraju is.
[intense music playing]
[pot breaks]
[thud]
[metal clanking]
[thud sounds continue]
[music intensifies]
Sister!
Help me!
Help!
Thanks, sister.
Get inside. Go!
[thud sounds continue]
You asked what she
was doing in the forest?
Now you know.
So, she is a good girl...
with a bad past.
[furniture breaks]
Get inside.
[gasps] He's coming.
[thud sounds continue]
I'll pluck your eyeballs, you idiot!
The bleeding is under control.
Just try to relax.
What a bunch of losers!
They want to be these badass goons.
But they can't fight to save their life.
[thud sounds continue]
[grunts]
[furniture breaks]
[revolver clicks]
[music intensifies]
[thud]
[gun shot fired]
Bro, the guns are here!
So you finally decided to show up?
Get in there! Now!
[gun shots firing]
[door creaks]
Come with me.
Let's block that door with a table.
Flip it.
-Come, let's go!
-Follow me, guys.
Watch out!
[suspenseful music playing]
[gun shots continue]
Swarna...
Should we escape from the back?
[groans]
[knife whooshes]
Sharath!
[groans]
Dad!
Don't worry, Sharath. We got you.
-What happened?
-Stop panicking and grab a cloth.
Hurry up! He's bleeding.
Sharath, just hang in there.
Press on it.
Guys, you need to leave right now!
Hurry up! We don't have time.
What about you, Swarna?
You guys leave first.
-We can't leave you and go.
-You said we should stick together.
I know. But I need you to go.
I will see you soon.
Ani, get them out safely.
Why are you being stubborn?
Ani, I'll hold the fort here.
You get them out from the back door.
I'll be with you shortly. Please go.
How can we leave her behind?
[gun shots continue]
Hurry up!
Come, come!
Guys, hurry!
Swarna, come quickly.
[melancholic music playing]
[gun shots continue]
He lost a lot of blood.
He needs you there.
I'll be with Swarna. You go.
Okay. Be careful.
I brought some more bullets for you.
Do you know how to load a gun?
I watched too many action
movies to not know. Watch me slay!
I'm back, sister!
Let's come on!
[intense music playing]
[gun shots continue]
[groans]
Sister...
-Oh, no! Are you okay?
-Give me the gun.
-There are only two bullets.
-How will you manage?
-You guys go!
-We can't leave without you.
I said, go!
I'll join you soon. Just go!
-Come.
-Be careful.
[groans]
[gun shots continue]
I've created a monster with my own hands.
[vehicle engine revs]
[vehicle storming in]
[wall shatters]
[groans]
[shrieks in pain]
Do I really need this right now?
Breaking into your house
by tearing the walls down.
I told you, didn't I?
This whole family thing
won't work out for you.
But you were adamant.
Now look.
You rained hell on the wedding house.
[thud]
[groaning] Let's go.
What haven't I done for you?
Have you no gratitude?
[rod clinks]
Have you forgotten everything, Jhansi?
I gave you that name, remember?
You owe that name...
and your whole life to me!
I'm the one who created you.
-I'm your God.
-[rod whooshes]
[screams]
God? Are you serious?
Are you real right now?
You found me at a time
I didn't know between right and wrong.
You brainwashed me into thinking...
you were God, and what you
said were the ultimate prophecy.
But people change.
We eventually uncover the truth.
You are not God, after all.
You're a monster that slowly
sucks the life out of someone.
Jhansi died the day
she realized the truth.
But I made one mistake though.
Instead of jail,
I should've sent you to hell.
[rod whooshes]
[gun clicks]
Go ahead and try!
I'll take you along with me.
[rod whooshes]
[gun shot fired]
[groans]
You hit the right spot.
I won't make it anymore.
Jhansi...
You think I'm still scared of dying?
[coughs]
[panting] Just look at yourself!
Let me repeat your math back to you.
When I die,
I have people who would mourn for me.
[groans]
People who would miss me.
But when you die,
people would celebrate
and call it good riddance.
Shut your eyes for 5 minutes.
Do some meditation.
You'll understand what I'm saying.
Now be gone.
I'll be gone.
But only after I watch you die.
That's when I'll die.
Let's see about that.
[gasps]
Let's...
Let's see.
[matchstick strikes]
Did you get used to your in-laws' routine?
-They only got used to mine.
-As expected.
Mother-in-law!
Sing the prayer, dear.
Shall I sing?
-Sure?
-I learned it.
Go ahead.
[singing off-key)
[everyone singing]
[intense music sets in]
Who is this guy, walking right in?
Who are you, sir?
My wife...
Stop. Who are you?
The last guy who showed up
like this gave us a lot of trouble.
-Who are you here for?
-My wife.
She said she's going to her
friend and never came back.
-Oh, you're Kiranmayi's husband?
-Hmm.
Come, you're family now.
Come in. You're really
famous in our family.
Look who it is. Kiranmayi's husband.
She came here because he was hitting her.
-You should be ashamed.
-What?
-You shouldn't have done that.
-What are you saying?
-I would've sent you to jail.
-Jail?
-Kiranmayi... Kiranmayi...
-My dear.
I said I'd come
in 2 days, right?
Why did you come running?
I told you my husband
can't stay away for long.
The last time you said 2
days, you stayed for a week.
So I didn't make the
mistake of waiting this time.
My friend insisted that I stay.
Bless me. You came all the way.
Look, he's hitting her again.
I'm not hitting her. I'm saying hi.
What did you tell them?
They're trying to send me to jail.
I told a small lie for
my friend, that's it.
Friend, friend, friend!
I want to talk to your friend right now!
-Are you the friend?
-I'm sorry.
I only asked her to come.
Sorry? You think that would suffice?
I'm doing all the house chores,
wiping my kids' asses. It's painful.
What kind of friendship is this?
Behind every best wife, there's a
best husband waiting for her at home.
What's wrong?
I've had quite the rough life as a kid.
Why mention it now?
I wanted a family and a
home that I could call my own.
No, no. He didn't mean to ask.
I bought ribbons and
talcum powder for her...
with the money I saved at the orphanage.
You don't have to go
that far back in time.
Let her speak.
Then a family adopted
her, leaving me behind.
Swarna, I'll make him sit
down and tell the whole story.
-Sure.
-100%.
-And you will listen?
-Yes, only if she narrates it like you.
Awesome.
You should be happy.
And don't worry. She will
stay right here, and so will I.
We will stay in a small room, don't worry.
I'm here for you.
Don't cry, dear.
Your friend is gold.
Bangaram (gold in Telugu)
Same thing.